twittercounter.com 2018-09-26

# Twitter Counter Data and Customer Content

Introduction
TwitterCounter B.V and its affiliates (“​Twitter Counter​” or "TC") are committed to
protecting the privacy of all individuals who:
     ● visit any websites or mobile sites offered by Twitter Counter, including
        without limitation t​ wittercounter.com​, and including all subdomains, present
        and future (the “​Website​”);
     ● use the mobile applications that TC makes available from time to time (the
        "​Applications​");
     ● use the Services including Twitter Counter Free, Individual, Professional,
        Business, Unlimited and other TC products and services (the "​Platforms​");
        and
"​Services​" are TC's platforms, websites and other properties. When we talk about
“Personal Information”, we mean information relating to you or other identifiable
individuals.
It is TC’s policy to respect your privacy and the privacy of all users of the Services.
This Privacy Policy has been established to help you understand our commitment to
protecting your privacy and personal data, and the steps we take to ensure it. By
visiting and/or using any of the Services, you agree to be bound by the terms of the
present Privacy Policy (the “​Privacy Policy​”). Where the present Privacy Policy refers
to “TC”, it may refer to the Services or to TwitterCounter B.V, depending on the
context.
Twitter Counter reserves the right, at any time, to modify or replace the Privacy
Policy. Please check the Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your use of the
Services following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes
acceptance of those changes.
Twitter Counter’s Privacy Policy forms part of its wider terms of service. Additional
terms may apply to other Services purchased. To make this policy easier to read,
any applicable Twitter Counter terms of service are referred to as the “​Terms​”. Both
the Terms and the Privacy Policy apply to your use of the Services.
Twitter Counter Data and Customer Content
We collect Personal Information (such as registration and account information)
from our customers and users of the Services for our own purposes, such as to
provide and administer the Services (“​Twitter Counter Data​”). We’re the data
controller in respect of this information.

We also process Personal Information on behalf of our customers as their data
processor, such as content generated, requested or published via the Platforms in
accordance with the instructions our customers give us through the Services
(including, for example, the information our customers monitor or collect from
social media sites like Twitter through the Services) (“​Customer Content​”). Our
customers control how their Customer Content is collected and used by them. In
legal terms this means that our customers are the data controller of their Customer
Content. Accordingly, we only use Customer Content to provide the Services to our
customers in accordance with the lawful instructions they give us through the
Services.
About this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how and when Twitter Counter collects, uses and
shares Twitter Counter Data when you use the Services. Twitter Counter receives
your information through our Website, Platforms and Applications.
Whilst most of this Privacy Policy relates to Twitter Counter Data, we also provide
some information about how our customers choose to collect and use Customer
Content through the Services.
The Services by their nature allow our customers to connect their accounts through
the APIs of our Supported Platforms (such as Twitter). This Privacy Policy does not
cover any information or other content you can view via the Services on Supported
Platforms (but which was not posted there using the Services). While we attempt to
facilitate access only to those Supported Platforms that share our respect for your
privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of any
Supported Platforms. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of
any Supported Platforms you access...
Twitter Counter Data we receive or collect
When you first register for a Twitter Counter account, and when you use the
Services, we collect some Personal Information about you such as:
    ● your full name and email address. We may also collect other contact details
    ● the geographic area where you use your computer and mobile devices
    ● a unique Twitter Counter user ID (an alphanumeric string) which is assigned
        to you upon registration
    ● other optional information as part of your account profile

   ● your IP Address and, when applicable, timestamp related to your consent
       and confirmation of consent
   ● other information submitted by you or your organizational representatives
       via various methods (email, online forms, surveys, etc)
   ● your billing details and any necessary other information to complete any
       financial transaction, and when making purchases through the Services, we
       may also collect your credit card or PayPal information
   ● user generated content (such as messages, posts, comments, pages, profiles,
       images, feeds or communications exchanged on the Supported Platforms)
   ● images or other files that you may publish via our Services
   ● information we may receive relating to communications you send us, such as
       queries, support tickets or comments concerning our Services
   ● information relating to an individual’s real time location
Twitter Counter also automatically collects and receives certain information from
your computer or mobile device, including the activities you perform on our
Website, the Platforms, and the Applications, the type of hardware and software
you are using (for example, your operating system or browser), and information
obtained from cookies (see “Cookies and Related Technologies” below). For
example, each time you visit the Website or otherwise use the Services, we
automatically collect your IP address, browser and device type, access times, the
web page from which you came, the regions from which you navigate the web page,
and the web page(s) you access (as applicable).
How we use Twitter Counter Data
Twitter Counter uses Twitter Counter Data for the following general purposes:
   ● to identify you when you login to your account
   ● to enable us to operate the Services and provide them to you
   ● to verify your transactions and for purchase confirmation, billing, security,
       and authentication
   ● to analyze the Website or the other Services and information about our
       visitors and users, including research into our user demographics and user
       behaviour in order to improve our content and Services
   ● to contact you about your account and provide customer service support,
       including responding to your comments and questions
   ● to share aggregate (non-identifiable) statistics about users of the Services to
       prospective advertisers and partners

    ● to keep you informed about the Services, features, surveys, newsletters,
        offers, contests and events we think you may find useful or which you have
        requested from us
    ● to sell or market Twitter Counter products and services to you
    ● to better understand your needs and the needs of users in the aggregate,
        diagnose problems, analyze trends, improve the features and usability of the
        Services, and better understand and market to our customers and users
    ● to keep the Services safe and secure
We also use non-identifiable information gathered for statistical purposes to keep
track of the number of visits to the Services with a view to introducing
improvements and improving usability of the Services.
Customer Content we process for our customers
Twitter Counter is a social media analytics and management tool.
Services help our customers optimize social media campaigns and marketing;
engaging audiences; and analyze the results.
In particular, the various Services allow our customers to instantly connect to other
third party services, including “Supported Platforms” such as Twitter, etc. When our
customers link a Supported Platform to their Twitter Counter account, our
customers can choose to instantly collect, process, share and access such
Supported Platform via their Twitter Counter account (subject to the terms of the
license agreements with the Supported Platforms).
In this way, our customers can obtain, use and analyze Personal Information from
Supported Platforms, and also create, input, submit, post, transmit, store, view,
display or share Personal Information through the functionality in the Services.
Such information can include Personal Information of all types, including but not
limited to the following categories:
    ● user generated content (such as messages (including direct or private
        messages), posts, comments, pages, profiles, images, feeds or
        communications exchanged on the Supported Platforms)
    ● contact details (such as name, email address, telephone number)
    ● additional individual information (such as age, gender, employer, profession,
        geographic location, education information, financial status, habits and
        preferences)
    ● information relating to individual’s real time location

Consent
By using any of the Services, or submitting or collecting any Personal Information
via the Services, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage disclosure, and use
of your Personal Information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do
not consent to the use of your Personal Information in these ways, please stop
using the Services.
Cookies and related technologies
Twitter Counter uses tracking technology (“​cookies​”) on the Website, and possibly
later also in the Applications, and in the Platforms, including mobile application
identifiers and a unique Twitter Counter user ID to help us recognize you across
different Services, to monitor usage and web traffic routing for the Services, and to
customize and improve the Services. By visiting the Website or using the Services
you agree to the use of cookies in your browser and HTML-based emails. Cookies
are small text files placed on your device when you visit a website, in order to track
use of the site and to improve your user experience.
Session Cookies
The Services use “session cookies”, which improve your user experience by storing
certain information from your current visit on your device, such as log-in
information. These enable us to remember your log-in session so you can move
easily within the Website or the other Services. Without these session cookies, we
wouldn’t be able to provide the Services to you. These session cookies have limited
functionalities and expirations, and you will be required to re-enter your Twitter
log-in information after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against
others accidentally accessing your account contents and related Personal
Information. Other examples of our use of session cookies include to track the
number of visits by a particular visitor to a page and to store items in an online
shopping cart for the Shop.
Remarketing Cookies
Partners who help us serve advertising off the Website and analytics companies
may also put cookies on your device. We use several third-party vendors to help
deliver ads for relevant Twitter Counter products and services to you when you visit

certain third-party sites. We may share with third-party ad partners a cryptographic
hash of a common account identifier (such as an email address), to help us
measure and tailor ads and services provided to you. Below is information about
one such vendor. Please note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies
and does not include use of cookies by any third parties.
i)          Google Analytics
Twitter Counter uses a specific cookie in order to facilitate the use of Google
Universal Analytics for users logged-in to the Applications or the Platforms
(“Logged-In User). If you are a Logged-In User, Twitter Counter may use your Twitter
Counter user ID in combination with Google Universal Analytics and Google
Analytics to track and analyze the pages of the Services you visit. We do this only to
better understand how you use the Website and the other Services, with a view to
offering improvements for all Twitter Counter users; and to tailor our business and
marketing activities accordingly, both generally and specifically to you. Google
Analytics cookies do not provide Twitter Counter with any Personal Information.
When we may share Personal Information
Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, Twitter Counter does not divulge any
Personal Information gathered via the Services (including Customer Content) to
third parties.
Notwithstanding anything in the Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may share any
information we have collected about you or Customer Content:
(1) when you consent to the disclosure of such information to a third party when
connecting to a third-party service that asks you if you consent to such sharing;
(2) where we are legally required to do so, such as in response to court orders or
legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or to defend
against legal claims or demands;
(3) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action
regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the
rights, property, or personal safety of any person;
(4) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding
situations that involve abuse of the Services infrastructure or the Internet in general
(such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to
compromise the security of the Website infrastructure or the Services generally);
(5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity (in which case we will
require such entity to assume our obligations under this Privacy Policy or inform
you that you are covered by a new privacy policy); and

(6) if this information is not private, is aggregated or is otherwise non-Personal
Information, such as your public user profile information and related public data
(such as Tweets, likes, etc.) or the number of users who clicked on a particular link
(even if only one did so).
Subject to obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, we may also disclose
information to our affiliates, agents, contractors, and service providers in order to
facilitate the functioning of the Services or to perform tasks that are integral to the
Services, such as processing transactions, fulfilling requests for information, or
providing support services or other tasks, from time to time. Information may also
be transferred from Twitter Counter to the third parties in control of the Supported
Platforms, but only to the extent required in order for the Services to function
properly.
Security
We use industry best practices to keep any information collected and/or
transmitted to the Supported Platforms or Third-Party Apps secure. This includes
the use of HTTPS, which encrypts all transmitted data, and OAuth 2.0 protocols for
authentication and data transfer to Supported Platforms.
In addition, Twitter Counter uses third-party vendors and hosting partners such as
Google Cloud Platform to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking,
storage, and related technology required to run the Services. These vendors have
been selected for their high standards of both physical and technological security.
When payments are processed via credit card, Twitter Counter uses third-party
vendors that are PCI-DSS Compliant. At no point does Twitter Counter have access
to your credit card information nor are your payment method details saved by
Twitter Counter.
You should bear in mind that submission of information over the Internet is never
entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of information you submit via
the Services whilst it is in transit over the Internet and any such submission is at
your own risk, and this risk is specifically disclaimed in our Terms.
If you are a Logged-in User, it is advisable that you log out of your account at the
end of every session and not leave a logged-in account unattended for any period
of time, particularly if you use a shared computer or device.
Information storage and international transfers

TwitterCounter B.V, the entity which provides the Services, is a Dutch company with
its head-office located in Amsterdam, Noord Holland. For the purposes of EU data
protection law, the Netherlands is considered a country which provides adequate
protections for Personal Information, as confirmed by the European Commission in
Commission Decision 2002/2/EC​.
The Services are mainly provided from our offices in Amsterdam. However, by the
very nature of the Services, the data that is viewed, collected, stored or posted on or
through the Services also needs to flow from wherever you are located in the world,
to where our Supported Platforms are storing the same data (i.e. in most cases, in
the United States). In addition, Twitter Counter uses third-party service providers
(such as managed hosting providers, card processors, CRM systems, sub-processors
of Customer Content and technology partners) to provide the necessary hardware,
software, networking, storage and other services that we use to operate the
Services. These third party providers may process, or store, the same Customer
Content on servers outside of the EEA, including in the US.
By using any of the Services, or submitting or collecting any Personal Information
via the Services, you authorize Twitter Counter and its authorized service partners
to use and process Customer Content and Twitter Counter Data (including any
Personal Information) in these countries. Please be aware that the privacy
protections and the rights of authorities and Government agencies to access your
Personal Information in some of these countries may not be equivalent to those in
your country.
For our customers with a principal location in the EU:
If you primarily use the Services within the EU, we will process Customer Content
(which may include Personal Information) as a data processor on your behalf.
Under EU law, you are considered to be the data controller of the Customer
Content, and as such you are responsible for complying with applicable data
protection laws in respect of the processing of Customer Content and the lawful
instructions you give us.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ​contact us​.
Email preferences
You may opt out of marketing communications sent by Twitter Counter by
managing your email preferences on our E    ​ mail Preferences Management page​, or
by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each marketing email.

Your rights
You can c​ ontact us​ to obtain a copy of the Personal Information held about you by
us. This may be subject to a fee not exceeding any prescribed fee permitted by
applicable law. You can also ask us to correct and, where relevant, erase that
information. Please note that certain Personal Information may need to be retained
by Twitter Counter for a period of time following cancellation of your account where
this is necessary for our legitimate business purposes or required or authorized by
applicable law. As mentioned above you have a right to change your email
preferences at any time.
You should be aware that Twitter Counter acts as a conduit between our users and
the Supported Platforms. In several instances, the content published via Twitter
Counter will not be in Twitter Counter’s custody or control, and any content that has
been shared by you through any Supported Platform via the Services may continue
to be available to third parties and the public at large, as this content is now under
the control of the operators of the Supported Platforms.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact:
Twitter Counter
or:
TwitterCounter B.V
Singel 542
Amsterdam, 1017 AZ
The Netherlands
